http://www.cchs.com/privacy-policy

Navigation
Skip to Content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Effective 1/1/2020 This policy applies to the following URLs owned and operated by Cinch Home Services, Inc. (collectively "Cinch," "we," "us," or "our"):
www.cinchhomeservices.com http://www.cchs.com  http://www.hmsriskmanagement.com  http://www.totalprotect.com   http://www.placemyclaim.com  http://www.systemsprotect.com  http://www.appliancebuyline.com  http://www.hmsnational.com
This policy describes how Cinch collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites that display a link to this policy. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at erelations@cinchhs.com. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request. Notice to California residents If you are a California resident, please see our Supplemental Privacy Notice for California Residents for more information on your privacy rights. FACTS: WHAT DOES CINCH DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This type of information can include:
Full name, Address, phone number and email address Account transactions and purchase history The date and time you contact us, the nature of your inquiry, and related information, when you access our website Credit card, loan number or ACH payment information
When applying for a career with us and when applying as a service provider, we also collect additional information from you as need to fulfill your request. We may receive information about you from other sources such as third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.  If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from third parties include purchased marketing data about our customers that is combined with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products. We use this information to:
Verify coverage is available in your area and provide pricing quotes Deliver requested quote and product information Aggregate website usage data to make site improvements Calculate applicable sales tax and complete your purchase Deliver helpful email newsletters and account information to customers Contact you to fulfill service and other requests
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to protect your information as described in this notice. Access: Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by emailing our Customer Support at compliance@cinchhs.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. We will retain your information as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide you services; and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. For Quality Assurance purposes, both inbound and outbound service calls may be recorded. How? All companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information, the reasons Cinch chooses to share and whether you can limit this sharing. Who? We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Cinch share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes — such as to process your transactions, maintain your account, or to respond to court orders and legal investigations. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request. If Cinch is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes — to offer relevant products and services to you
YES, BUT WE SHARE ONLY WITH MARKETING SERVICE PROVIDERS UNDER NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENTS
YES - YOU MAY OPT OUT
For joint marketing with other companies
NO
WE DON'T SHARE
For our home service providers' everyday business purposes — information to help them complete your requested transactions such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide the services to us.
YES
NO
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your transactions and experiences
YES
NO
For our everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
NO
WE DON'T SHARE
For our non-affiliates to market to you
NO
WE DON'T SHARE
WHO WE ARE Who is providing this notice? Cinch Home Services, Inc.   WHAT WE DO How does Cinch protect my personal information? To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). How does Cinch collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:  Apply for a home warranty Register your product or service online File a claim or otherwise use your product, in writing, online or by phone Pay your bill
Why can't I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness affiliates from using your information to market to you sharing for non-affiliates to market to you State laws and individual companies may give you additional right to limit sharing.
DEFINITIONS Affiliates Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Our affiliates include companies like Cross Country Home Services, Inc. and HMS National, Inc. Non-affiliates Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. We do not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you. Cookies Cookies are small files that websites put on your computer hard drive when you first visit. Cookies indicate how often you visit web pages, which helps us learn what information interests you. They let you store preferences and user names, register products and services, and personalize pages. Cookies are not software. They cannot be programmed, cannot carry viruses, and cannot install malware on your computer. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION Types of email communication we send you Service-related announcements We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. We may also send you email to communicate with you about servicing a home warranty claim. If you request access codes to the Appliance Buyline service as a benefit of your warranty plan, those codes will be emailed to you. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. Please contact our customer service team at (877) 248-6683 for information on deactivating your account. Renewal notifications We may also send you email to notify you when it is time to renew your warranty. You may opt out of renewal notifications by following the Unsubscribe or Opt-out instructions found in the email message. Homeowner tips On occasion, as a benefit of your home warranty membership, we may also send you emails containing tips for maintaining your appliances and home systems. You may opt out of these notifications by following the Unsubscribe or Opt-out instructions found in the email message. Use of cookies Technologies such as cookies or similar technologies are used by us and our partners, including marketing partners and agencies, affiliates, analytics service providers, service partners, and online customer support providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember user settings, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. Content you may create or upload to our sites Any content created and uploaded to one of our websites becomes the property of the website and can be used in marketing or promotional material without compensation to the provider. Behavioral targeting/re-targeting We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here.  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads. Log files As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services, marketing, analytics, and site functionality. Customer testimonials, comments and reviews We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our Website which may contain personal information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from testimonials or comments please contact us at erelations@cinchhs.com. Blog/Forum
Our Website may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at erelations@cinchhs.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. Referrals If you choose to use our referral service to refer a contractor to us, we will ask you for the contractor's name, email address and phone number, as well as additional information about the contractor. We will use this information to recruit the provider into our Service Network. We store this information for the sole purpose of recruitment initiatives. The contractor may contact us at (800) 531-3466 to request that we remove this information from our database. We may also collect, from you, personal information about your contacts such as first and last name when you provide an additional customer. When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided. If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below. Links to other websites Our site includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. Social media widgets Our Websites or Blogs include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, Widgets such as Share This, or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them. NOTIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your personal information or make any material change, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Contact us: Cinch Home Services, Inc. 4700 Exchange Court, Suite 300 Boca Raton, FL 33431 Company main: (800) 778-8000 erelations@cinchhs.com
Privacy Policy (Updated 1/1/2020) CA Privacy Notice Terms of Use Disclosure Site Map
©2020 Cinch Home Services, Inc.
All rights reserved. Cinch is a registered mark of Cinch Home Services, Inc.
©2020 Cinch Home Services, Inc. All rights reserved.
Cinch is a registered mark of Cinch Home Services, Inc.
